var triviaArray = [
	{	'Question': 'What team did Babe Ruth play for before joining the Boston Red Sox?',
		'Answers': ['Boston Braves','Baltimore Orioles','New York Yankees','Cincinnati Reds'],
		'Correct': 1,
		'Info': 'Impressed with Ruth\'s pitching abilities, Joe Engel, a former Mount St. Mary\'s student, along with a teacher at St. Mary\'s, Brother Gilbert, brought Ruth to the attention of Jack Dunn, owner and manager of the then minor-league Baltimore Orioles. After watching Ruth pitch in a workout for half an hour, Dunn signed Ruth to a contract. He signed a contract for $250 a month on February 14, 1914.'
	},
	{	'Question': 'What team moved to D.C. to become the Washington Nationals in 2005?',
		'Answers': ['Tokyo Giants','Brooklyn Dodgers','Kansas City Monarchs','Montreal Expos'],
		'Correct': 3,
		'Info': 'The end of the legal fight to keep the Expos in Montreal came on November 15, when arbitrators struck down a lawsuit by the former team owners against MLB and former majority owner Jeffrey Loria. The MLB franchise owners approved the move to Washington in a 28-1 vote on December 3. Baltimore Orioles owner Peter Angelos cast the sole "nay" vote, resenting the franchise\'s relocation and intrusion into the Baltimore/D.C. market.'
	},
	{	'Question': 'Who has played the most consecutive games of baseball, breaking Lou Gehrig\'s record on September 6, 1995?',
		'Answers': ['Barry Bonds','Cal Ripken, Jr.','Mark McGuire','Moises Alou'],
		'Correct': 1,
		'Info': 'On September 6, 1995, many baseball fans within and out of the United States tuned in to cable TV network ESPN to watch Ripken surpass Lou Gehrig\'s 56-year-old record for consecutive games played (2,130 games). The game, between the Orioles and the California Angels, still ranks as one of the network\'s most watched baseball games (Baseball\'s most-watched game was Game 7 of the 1986 World Series). Cal\'s children, Rachel and Ryan, threw out the ceremonial first balls. Both President Bill Clinton and Vice President Al Gore were at the game. President Clinton was in the WBAL local radio broadcast booth when Ripken hit a home runin the fourth inning, and called the home run over the air. When the game became official after the Angels\' half of the fifth inning, the numerical banners that displayed Ripken\'s streak on the wall of the B&O Warehouse outside the stadium\'s right field wall changed from 2130 to 2131. Everyone attending (including the opposing Angels and all four umpires) erupted with a standing ovation lasting more than 22 minutes, one of the longest standing ovations for any athlete; ESPN did not go to a commercial break during the entire ovation. During the ovation, Ripken did a lap around the entire Camden Yards warning track to shake hands and give high-fives to the fans. The humble superstar had to be convinced by his teammates (who in fact playfully shoved him out of the dugout) to take a victory lap around the stadium, shaking hands and creating a highlight reel moment that\'s been replayed repeatedly in the ensuing years.'
	},
	{	'Question': 'What 1929 feat did Lee Richmond perform in a Major League Baseball first?',
		'Answers': ['He hit a grand slam.','He pitched a perfect game.','He had an unassisted triple play.','He stole home.'],
		'Correct': 1,
		'Info': 'Richmond struck out five, allowed only three balls to be hit out of the infield, and, remarkably, got one of his 27 outs when the right fielder threw the batter out at first base.'
	},
	{	'Question': 'Before playing in the majors, Jackie Robinson played with the minor league Montreal Royals, the top farm club of which organization?',
		'Answers': ['Brooklyn Dodgers','Milwaukee Brewers','St. Louis Cardinals','Chicago White Sox'],
		'Correct': 0,
		'Info': 'Six days before the start of the 1947 season, the Dodgers called Robinson up to the major leagues. With Eddie Stanky entrenched at second base for the Dodgers, Robinson played his initial major league season as a first baseman.'
	},
	{	'Question': 'What up-and-coming star player saw his first World Series with the Yankees in 1936 as Babe Ruth\'s "replacement"?',
		'Answers': ['Lou Gehrig','Joe DiMaggio','Carl Hubbell','Freddie Fitzsimmons'],
		'Correct': 1,
		'Info': 'In 1936, the Yankees played their first World Series without Babe Ruth and their first with Joe DiMaggio, Ruth having retired from the Yankees after the 1934 season.'
	},
	{	'Question': 'What is the oldest active ball park in Major League Baseball?',
		'Answers': ['Camden Yards','Kauffman Stadium','Wrigley Field','Fenway Park'],
		'Correct': 3,
		'Info': 'After two rain delays, Fenway Park finally hosted its first professional baseball game on April 20, 1912. (The first official game played in Fenway actually occurred on April 9 when the Sox beat Harvard University, 2-0.) The Red Sox defeated the New York Highlanders, later known as the Yankees, before 27,000 fans,7-6 in 11 innings. The event would have made front page news hadit not been for the sinking of the Titanic only a few days before.'
	},
	{	'Question': 'What player was accused of using too much pine tar on his bat on July 24, 1983, causing a game-winning home run to be nullified?',
		'Answers': ['Rich Gossage','George Brett','Gaylord Perry','Rocky Colavito'],
		'Correct': 1,
		'Info': 'With Brett watching from the dugout, McClelland and the rest of the umpiring crew inspected the bat. Measuring the bat against the width of home plate (which is 17 inches), they determined that the amount of pine tar on the bat\'s handle exceeded that allowed by Rule 1.10(b) of the Major League Baseball rule book, which read that "a bat may not be covered by such a substance more than 18 inches from the tip of the handle."'
	},
	{	'Question': 'What basketball great made the surprising decision to switch sports, signing a minor league baseball contract with the Chicago White Sox in 1994?',
		'Answers': ['Patrick Ewing','Shaquille O\'Neal','Michael Jordan','Karl Malone'],
		'Correct': 2,
		'Info': 'The White Sox were another team owned by Bulls owner Jerry Reinsdorf, who continued to honor Jordan\'s basketball contract during the years he played baseball. Jordan had a brief professional baseball career for the Birmingham Barons, a Chicago White Sox farm team, batting .202 with 3 HR, 51 RBI, 30 SB, and 11 errors. He also appeared for the Scottsdale Scorpions in the 1994 Arizona Fall League.'
	},
	{	'Question': 'What baseball announcer was famous for his signature phrase, "Holy Cow!"?',
		'Answers': ['Mel Allen','Joe Garagiola','Harry Carey','Vin Scully'],
		'Correct': 2,
		'Info': 'Harry Caray\'s trademark call of "Holy Cow!" and his enthusiastic singing of "Take me out to the ballgame" during the 7th inning stretch (as he had done with the White Sox) made Caray a fan favorite both locally and nationally. Harry occasionally had problems pronouncing names, to comic effect, such as his attempt at saying "Hector Villanueva" which was captured on WGN\'s memorial CD to Harry.'
	},
	{	'Question': 'Which team hosted the infamous "Disco Demolition Night" promotional event on July 12, 1979?',
		'Answers': ['Houston Astros','Chicago White Sox','Minnesota Twins','Florida Marlins'],
		'Correct': 1,
		'Info': 'Disco Demolition Night was a promotional event that took place on Thursday, July 12, 1979, at Comiskey Park in Chicago, Illinois. It was held during the twi-night doubleheader baseball game between the Chicago White Sox and the Detroit Tigers. During the climax of the event, rowdy fans surged onto the field, and a near riot ensued. It would ultimately prove to be one of the most notable promotional ideas and one of the most infamous since "Ten Cent Beer Night" in Cleveland in 1974. The event is regarded as the culmination of a backlash against disco music that had an effect on the decline of the genre.'
	},
	{	'Question': 'What country has contributed the most players to Major League Baseball outside of the United States?',
		'Answers': ['Japan','Cuba','Venezuela','Dominican Republic'],
		'Correct': 3,
		'Info': 'Baseball is by far the most popular sport in the Dominican Republic today. After the United States, the Dominican Republic has the second-highest number of baseball players in Major League Baseball (MLB). Some of the Dominican players have been regarded as among the best in the game.'
	},
	{	'Question': 'Who is the only pitcher in Major League Baseball to win a World Series games in three different decades?',
		'Answers': ['Whitey Ford','Jim Palmer','Bob Welch','Johnny Podres'],
		'Correct': 1,
		'Info': 'Jim Palmer is the only pitcher in big-league history to win World Series games in three decades (1966, 1970-71, 1983). One of his most amazing feats is that during his 20-year major league career of 575 games (including 17 postseason games), he never surrendered a grand slam.'
	},
	{	'Question': 'What pitcher ended Joe DiMaggio\'s 56-game hitting streak?',
		'Answers': ['Hal Newhouser','Jim Bagby','Al Smith','Mel Harder'],
		'Correct': 1,
		'Info': 'Bagby participated as a member of the Indians organization on the July 17, 1941 game where Joe DiMaggio\'s game hitting streak was halted at 56. His son, Jim Bagby, Jr., was also a major leaguer who played for the Red Sox, Indians and Pirates. The Bagbys became the first father and son to pitch in the World Series when Jim Jr. appeared for the 1946 Red Sox.'
	},
	{	'Question': 'In the mythology surrounding the Chicago Cubs, what curse is responsible for the team not reaching the World Series since 1945?',
		'Answers': ['The Curse of the Billy Goat','The Curse of the Bambino','The Curse of Coogan\'s Bluff','The Curse of Bartman'],
		'Correct': 0,
		'Info': 'The Billy Goat curse was supposedly placed on the Cubs in 1945 when Billy Goat Tavern owner Billy Sianis was asked to leave a World Series game at the Cubs\' home ground of Wrigley Field because his pet goat\'s odor was bothering other fans. He was outraged and declared, "Them Cubs, they aren\'t gonna win no more," which has been interpreted to mean that there would never be another World Series game won at Wrigley Field. The curse was immortalized in newspaper columns over the years, particularly by syndicated columnist Mike Royko, and gained widespread attention during the 2003 postseason when Fox television commentators played it up during the Cubs-Marlins match-up in the National League Championship Series.'
	},
	{	'Question': 'Who was the only member of the Cincinnati Reds\' "Big Red Machine" of the 1970\'s to be born and raised in Cincinnati?',
		'Answers': ['Dave Concepcion','Ken Griffey, Sr.','George Foster','Pete Rose'],
		'Correct': 3,
		'Info': 'The Cincinnati Reds of the 1970s earned the nickname "the Big Red Machine," and is widely acknowledged as one of the greatest teams ever. On a team with many great players, Rose, along with Hall of Famers Johnny Bench, Joe Morgan and Tony Perez, was viewed as one of the club\'s leaders. Rose was known for sliding headfirst into a base, his signature move. In the sport of Wakeboarding, there is a trick named "Pete Rose". The rider who invented the trick, Scott Byerly, said he would "slide like Pete Rose" upon crashing while trying to complete the maneuver. The last episode of Arrested Development, "Development Arrested", also references Rose\'s slide: "And although he [George Michael] had only gotten to second base, he\'d gone in head-first, like Pete Rose."'
	},
	{	'Question': '1998 saw a race between the St. Louis Cardinals\' Mark McGwire and the Chicago Cubs\' Sammy Sosa to break which player\'s 61 home run record?',
		'Answers': ['Babe Ruth','Albert Belle','Roger Maris','Joe DiMaggio'],
		'Correct': 2,
		'Info': 'The 1998 Major League Baseball home run chase in Major League Baseball was the race between first baseman Mark McGwire of the St. Louis Cardinals and right fielder Sammy Sosa of the Chicago Cubs that resulted in both players breaking Roger Maris\'s long-standing and highly coveted record of 61 home runs. McGwire broke Maris\'s record on September 8 against the Cubs and finished with 70 home runs. Sosa finished with 66.'
	},
	{	'Question': 'What baseball great is known for such colorful sayings as "It ain\'t over till it\'s over."',
		'Answers': ['Hank Aaron','Roger Clemens','Wade Boggs','Yogi Berra'],
		'Correct': 3,
		'Info': 'Berra, who quit school in the eighth grade, has a tendency toward malapropism and fracturing the English language in highly provocative, interesting ways. "It ain\'t over till it\'s over" is arguably the most famous example, often quoted. Simultaneously denying and confirming his reputation, Berra once stated, "I really didn\'t say everything I said."'
	},
	{	'Question': 'Where is the National Baseball Hall of Fame & Museum located?',
		'Answers': ['Oklahoma City, OK','Cooperstown, NY','Memphis, TN','Cleveland, OH'],
		'Correct': 1,
		'Info': 'The Hall of Fame was dedicated on June 12, 1939 by Lee Ferrick Andrews, grandson of Edward Clark, who was a founder of the Singer Sewing Machine Company. Stephen C. Clark was owner of a local hotel and sought to bring tourists to Cooperstown, which had been suffering economically when the Great Depression significantly reduced the local tourist trade and Prohibition devastated the local hops industry. His granddaughter, Jane Forbes Clark, is the current Chairman of the Board of Directors. The erroneous claim that U.S. Civil War hero Abner Doubleday invented baseball in Cooperstown, a claim made by former National League president Abraham G. Mills and his 1905 Mills Commission, was instrumental in the early marketing of the Hall.'
	},
	{	'Question': 'Which player has been awarded a record-setting seven Most Valuable player awards?',
		'Answers': ['Mickey Mantle','Barry Bonds','Stan Musial','Jimmie Foxx'],
		'Correct': 1,
		'Info': 'Barry Bonds accomplishments during his baseball career place him among the greatest baseball players of all-time. He has a record-setting seven Most Valuable Player awards, including a record-setting four consecutive MVPs. He is a fourteen-time All-Star and eight-time Gold Glove-winner. He holds numerous Major League Baseball records, including the all-time Major League Baseball home run record with 762 and the single-season Major League record for home runs with 73 (set in 2001), and is also the all-time career leader in both walks (2,558) and intentional walks (688).'
	},
	{	'Question': 'Where was the first Major League Baseball All-Star Game played?',
		'Answers': ['San Francisco, CA','Chicago, IL','Los Angeles, CA','New York, NY'],
		'Correct': 1,
		'Info': 'The first All-Star Game was held as part of the 1933 World\'s Fair in Chicago, Illinois, and was the brainchild of Arch Ward, then sports editor for The Chicago Tribune. Initially intended to be a one-time event, its great success resulted in making the game an annual one.'
	},
	{	'Question': 'Who holds the highest career batting average of all time?',
		'Answers': ['Stan Musial','Ty Cobb','Willie Mays','"Shoeless" Joe Jackson'],
		'Correct': 1,
		'Info': 'Cobb is widely credited with setting 90 Major League Baseball records during his career. He still holds several records, including the highest career batting average (.367) and most career batting titles with 11 (or 12, depending on source).'
	},
	{	'Question': 'What team did the White Sox throw the 1919 World Series to in the "Black Sox" Scandal?',
		'Answers': ['Cleveland Indians','St. Louis Browns','Cincinnati Reds','Baltimore Orioles'],
		'Correct': 2,
		'Info': 'The name "Black Sox" refers to the Chicago White Sox team from that era. Eight members of the major league franchise were banned for life from baseball for throwing (intentionally losing) games, and essentially giving the series to the Cincinnati Reds.'
	},
	{	'Question': 'What were baseballs wrapped in before the introduction of cowhide in 1974?',
		'Answers': ['Bisonhide','Beaver pelt','Buckskin','Horsehide'],
		'Correct': 3,
		'Info': 'The official major league ball is made by Rawlings, which produces the hand-stiched balls in Costa Rica. Rawlings became the official supplier to the majors in 1977, succeeding Spalding, which had supplied the official ball for a century. The cover of the ball was traditionally horsehide through 1973, but due to dwindling supplies cowhide was introduced in 1974.'
	},
	{	'Question': 'What year saw the introduction of the Knickerbocker Rules, which are widely considered the basis of the modern game of baseball?',
		'Answers': ['1912','1845','1931','1822'],
		'Correct': 1,
		'Info': 'In 1845 Cartwright and a committee from his Knickerbocker Base Ball Club, made up of volunteer firemen, drew up rules converting this playground game into a more elaborate and interesting sport to be played by adults. He and other firemen played on a field at 47th and 27th Streets. The rules of the modern game are based on their by-laws, and Cartwright is thought to be the first person to draw a diagram of a diamond shaped field.'
	}
]	